Guide to the David Price Papers, 1960-2006 and undated RL.01048
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Congressional Papers Record Group, 1981-1994 and undated
  - Press/Media Files Series, 1986-1994 and undated, 36 boxes
    - Press Releases Subseries, 1987-1994
      Releases from Price's office highlight information on new legislation, hearings to be held, issues important to North Carolinians, appearances by Price, and legislative initiatives. Arranged by year.
      - 1987, 2 folders (Box CPM-23)
      - 1988 (Box CPM-23)
      - 1989, 2 folders (Box CPM-23)
      - 1990, 3 folders (Box CPM-23)
      - 1991, 1 of 2 folders (Box CPM-23)
      - 1991, 2 of 2 folders (Box CPM-24)
      - 1992 (Box CPM-24)
      - 1993-1994, 103rd Congress Press Releases (Box CPM-24)
    - Mailings and Other Media Files Subseries, 1987-1994 and undated
      Many of the files pertain to franking privileges and targeted mailings; postal patron mailings sent to all in Price's district; newsletters, files related to Price's cable call-in show Keeping in Touch or another show Price took part in called Watch on Washington; or files related to his radio segment called Washington Report. Audio and videotapes of many of Price's broadcasts may be found in the Congressional Papers - District Office Files. In original order as received.
      - Franking OKs (Pre-103rd Congress), 2 folders (Box CPM-24)
      - Franking Approvals (Box CPM-24)
      - Franking Info (Box CPM-24)
      - Franking Approvals-Pending (Box CPM-24)
      - Targeted Mailings-101st Congress (Box CPM-24)
      - Targeted Mailings-102nd Congress (Box CPM-24)
      - Targeted Mail-Schedule, etc. (Box CPM-24)
      - Mailing List Procurement (Box CPM-24)
      - Community Meetings, Raleigh, Orange Co., 1993 Aug. 25-1993 Aug. 26, 1 of 2 folders (Box CPM-24)
      - Community Meetings, Raleigh, Orange Co., 1993 Aug. 25-1993 Aug. 26, 2 of 2 folders (Box CPM-25)
      - Newsletters, Notices, etc. (Box CPM-25)
      - Postal Patron, 1994 (Box CPM-25)
      - Other Newsletters (Box CPM-25)
      - Postal Patron #2, 1993 Fall (Box CPM-25)
      - Postal Patron #1 (proofs), 1993 (Box CPM-25)
      - 4th District Poll Results, Postal Patron #1, 1993 Spring/Summer (Box CPM-25)
      - 102nd Congress, Postal Patron #4 (Box CPM-25)
      - 102nd Congress, Postal Patron #3 (Box CPM-25)
      - 102nd Congress, Postal Patron #2 (Box CPM-25)
      - Poll Results-102nd Congress (Box CPM-25)
      - 102nd Congress, Postal Patron #1 (Box CPM-25)
      - Postal Patron #4-Family, 101st Congress (Box CPM-25)
      - Postal Patron #3, 101st Congress (Box CPM-25)
      - Postal Patron #2, 101st Congress-Constituent Service Newsletter (Box CPM-25)
      - 101st Congress Newsletter #1, 1989 Jan. (Box CPM-25)
      - Miscellaneous Newsletters (Box CPM-25)
      - Media Plan (Box CPM-25)
      - Events (Box CPM-25)
      - Schedule Advisories, 1993-1994 (Box CPM-25)
      - Raleigh Cablevision (Box CPM-26)
      - Speechwriting (Box CPM-26)
      - FCC Rules (Box CPM-26)
      - Press Conferences (Box CPM-26)
      - PSAs (Box CPM-26)
      - Watch on Washington Call-In (Box CPM-26)
      - Watch on Washington-102nd Congress (Box CPM-26)
      - Washington Report Scripts, 2 folders (Box CPM-26)
      - Radio Show, 103rd Congress (Box CPM-26)
      - Washington Report Scripts, 102nd Congress, 2 folders (Box CPM-26)
    - Clippings Subseries, 1987 Jan.-1994 Dec.
      Photocopied clippings documenting Price's legislation, public appearances, work on behalf of constituents, and his and his opponents' campaigns. Arranged chronologically.
      - 1987 Jan.-1988 Sept. Mar., 9 folders (Box CPM-27)
      - 1988 Oct.-1989 May, 10 folders (Box CPM-28)
      - 1989 June-1990 Feb., 10 folders (Box CPM-29)
      - 1990 Mar.-1991 June, 9 folders (Box CPM-30)
      - 1991 July-1994 Mar., 10 folders (Box CPM-31)
      - 1994 Apr.-1994 Dec., 4 folders (Box CPM-32)
    - Photographic Materials Subseries, circa 1985-1996 and undated
      Mainly photographs of Price and other political figures in various public appearances; some family photographs are also included. Many photographs contain very brief or no identification. To the extent possible, they have been arranged chronologically by year; within each year they are arranged alphabetically by subject.
      - circa 1985 (Box CPM-32)
        - Testimony, Bevill Subcommittee (Box CPM-32)
      - 1986
        - Freshman Orientation Activities and Unidentified Photographs (Box CPM-32)
        - Price for Congress and NASFAA (National Association of Student Financial Aid Administrators) (Box CPM-32)
        - Trip to Harvard (Box CPM-32)
      - 1986-1987 and undated
        - UPS visit and unidentified photographs (Box CPM-32)
      - 1987
        - Bill Friday's talk show, WUNC-TV (Box CPM-32)
        - Chinese officials (Box CPM-32)
        - Congressional Technology Literacy Walkthrough and unidentified photographs (Box CPM-32)
        - Tour of Fort Bragg (Box CPM-32)
        - Unidentified photographs (Box CPM-32)
      - 1987-1988 and undated
        - U.S. Postal Service and unidentified photographs (Box CPM-32)
      - 1987, 1989, and undated
        - Unidentified photographs (Box CPM-32)
      - 1988
        - American Airlines; Inco Alloys International; unidentified photographs; and miscellaneous pamphlets with Price photographs (Box CPM-32)
        - Community College Silver Anniversary (Box CPM-32)
        - Community meeting and unidentified photographs (Box CPM-32)
        - Congressional Art Competition Winner (Box CPM-32)
        - Farm breakfast and unidentified photographs (Box CPM-32)
        - Greek Archbishop (Box CPM-33)
        - HCA Holly Hill (Box CPM-33)
        - Price portraits, contact sheet (Box CPM-33)
        - Rep. Les Aspin breakfast (Box CPM-33)
        - Shaw University (Box CPM-33)
        - U.S. Postal Service (Box CPM-33)
        - Youth Leadership Council (Box CPM-33)
        - Unidentified photographs, 2 folders (Box CPM-33)
      - 1989
        - Arts Council Winners (Box CPM-33)
        - Atlantic Christian College graduation (Box CPM-33)
        - Banking Council (Box CPM-33)
        - Bush Inauguration (Box CPM-33)
        - Capital City Sertoma Club (Box CPM-33)
        - Chinese list (Box CPM-33)
        - Farm breakfast and unidentified photographs (Box CPM-33)
        - Frank Porter Graham Elementary School (Box CPM-33)
        - Funeral of Claude Pepper (Box CPM-33)
        - Lynn Road School Lecture (Box CPM-33)
        - NCAE (North Carolina Association of Educators) Field Hearing (Box CPM-33)
        - Needham B. Broughton High School Band (Box CPM-33)
        - Price at elementary school; staff Christmas party (Box CPM-33)
        - Price with a Trinity, N.C. youth (Box CPM-33)
        - Price with Alphatronix winners (Box CPM-33)
        - Price with interns (Box CPM-33)
        - Price with senior interns (Box CPM-33)
        - Price with summer interns (Box CPM-33)
        - Salute Program (Box CPM-33)
        - School groups, 3 folders (Box CPM-33)
        - Shearon Harris, 1989 (Box CPM-33)
        - Sunbelt Conference (Box CPM-33)
        - "Understanding Congress" Research Conference (Box CPM-33)
        - Underwood Elementary School visit to Washington (Box CPM-33)
        - U.S. Postal Service (Box CPM-33)
        - U.S. Congressmen David Price, Martin Lancaster, Sonny Montgomery, and Tim Valentine (Box CPM-33)
        - Veterans Conference (Box CPM-33)
        - Winners of Art Competition (Box CPM-33)
        - Youth Leadership Council (Box CPM-33)
        - Unidentified photographs, 1-4 of 5 folders (Box CPM-33)
        - Unidentified photographs, 5 of 5 folders (Box CPM-34)
      - 1990
        - Academy Reception (Box CPM-34)
        - Baptist Church Youth Choir (Box CPM-34)
        - Chancellor Kohl(?) (Box CPM-34)
        - Democratic Caucus Issues Conference (Box CPM-34)
        - DLC (Democratic Leadership Council) Visit (Box CPM-34)
        - Eisenhower Centennial (Box CPM-34)
        - Elementary school (Box CPM-34)
        - Hospitalized Veterans Week (Box CPM-34)
        - Interns and middle school (Box CPM-34)
        - Meredith Teaching Fellows (Box CPM-34)
        - Next Century School (Box CPM-34)
        - North Carolina Department of Transportation (Box CPM-34)
        - North Carolina State University (Box CPM-34)
        - Plasma Energy Corporation (Box CPM-34)
        - Political Americana photos (Box CPM-34)
        - Price with student (Box CPM-34)
        - School groups, 3 folders (Box CPM-34)
        - Youth Leadership Kids and Teacher of the Year (Box CPM-34)
      - 1991
        - Agriculture Subcommittee hearing (Box CPM-34)
        - American Political Science Association Award Ceremony (Box CPM-34)
        - Art winner (Box CPM-34)
        - Asheboro Fall Festival (Box CPM-34)
        - Chamber of Commerce with Price and Tim Valentine (Box CPM-34)
        - EPA groundbreaking (Box CPM-34)
        - Higher Education Hearing (Box CPM-34)
        - North Carolina Department of Agriculture (Box CPM-34)
        - Price with President George H. W. Bush (Box CPM-34)
        - Price with veterans (Box CPM-34)
        - Seniors luncheon (Box CPM-34)
      - 1992
        - Boy Scout troop (Box CPM-34)
        - Community college seminar (Box CPM-34)
        - North Carolina Biotechnology Center, building dedication (Box CPM-34)
        - North Carolina State University (Box CPM-34)
        - Price with President George H. W. Bush (Box CPM-34)
        - Town meeting (Box CPM-34)
        - Unidentified photographs, 1992 and undated (Box CPM-34)
      - 1993 (Box CPM-35)
        - Academy reception (Box CPM-35)
        - Boy Scout troop, school group, and unidentified photographs, 1993 and undated (Box CPM-35)
        - Christa McAuliffe Award Winner (Box CPM-35)
        - Farm breakfast (Box CPM-35)
        - School groups, 1993 and undated (Box CPM-35)
        - School groups and unidentified photographs, 1993 and undated (Box CPM-35)
        - Siemens and unidentified photographs, 1993 and undated (Box CPM-35)
        - Unidentified photographs, 1993 and undated (Box CPM-35)
      - 1994
        - Dedication of Talking Rock Trail (Box CPM-35)
        - Franklin Court (Box CPM-35)
        - Marketplace (Box CPM-35)
        - North Carolina Farm Bureau (Box CPM-35)
        - North Carolina's Watch on Washington, with Price, Mel Watt, and Howard Coble (Box CPM-35, Oversize-box OVSZ 1)
        - Price with school groups and unidentified photographs, 1994-1995 and undated (Box CPM-35)
      - 1996
        - Campaign photographs and brochures (Box CPM-35)
      - Undated photographs
        - Crime hearing (Box CPM-35)
        - David Price portrait (Oversize-box OVSZ 1)
        - Durham VA Medical Center visit (Box CPM-35)
        - Farm breakfast (Box CPM-35)
        - Franklin County Regional Medical Center (Box CPM-35)
        - Girl Scout (Box CPM-35)
        - Jesse Jackson (Box CPM-35)
        - Literacy summit and unidentified photographs (Box CPM-35)
        - Passport/visa photographs (Box CPM-36)
        - Price campaign (Box CPM-36)
        - Price on North Carolina's Watch on Washington, with Terry Sanford et al., 2 folders (Oversize-box OVSZ 1)
        - Price portraits, contact sheet (Box CPM-36)
        - Price with Billy Yearsin, Bruce Shands, and George Wilson (Box CPM-36)
        - Price with George H. W. Bush and unidentified photographs (Box CPM-36)
        - Price with representatives of Orange County's Adolescent Parenting Program (Box CPM-36)
        - Price with student (Box CPM-36)
        - Rhône-Poulenc (Box CPM-36)
        - School group (Box CPM-36)
        - School group and slides (Box CPM-36)
        - Summer interns (Box CPM-36)
        - Unidentified photographs, 13 folders (Box CPM-36)
- Campaign Office Files Record Group, 1982-1997 and undated
  Series within this record group are devoted to particular campaigns, but there is overlap in content from one campaign to another due to recurrence of issues, themes, and constituencies. There is no series for the 1992 campaign, but some materials for that year appear in the Various Campaigns Subseries. Following the individual campaigns are several general subseries that cover multiple campaigns and center on such topics as precinct analysis, redistricting, and polling. Finally, the Audiovisual Materials Series documents Price's campaigns and other media appearances. Primary arrangement of series is chronological for the biennial campaigns from 1986-1996; within these series, original arrangement by topic is retained.
  - 1986 Campaign Series, 13 boxes
    - News Clips, 1985 Apr.-1986 Apr., 8 folders (Box ACA-1)
    - Cobey Launches Bid for House re-election, Article, Raleigh Times, 1986 Feb. 12 (Box ACA-1)
    - Cobey Launches Bid for House seat, Article, N and O; [News and Observer], 1986 Feb. 12 (Box ACA-1)
    - Woodard Gets Funds from 3 Finance PACs, Article, N and O, 1986 Feb. 11 (Box ACA-1)
    - 4 Democrats Tee Off on Cobey, Article, DMH [Durham Morning Herald], 1986 Feb. 6 (Box ACA-1)
    - Price Leads in Fundraising for Race in 4th District, Article, N and O, 1986 Feb. 1 (Box ACA-1)
    - Price Off and Running in 4th District, Article, DMH, 1985 Oct. 24 (Box ACA-1)
    - Price Opens Campaign for 4th District, Article, Durham Sun, 1985 Oct. 25 (Box ACA-1)
    - Price Launches Campaign-Fresh Approach, Article, Raleigh Times, 1985 Oct. 23 (Box ACA-1)
    - Price Announces Candidacy, Article, CH [Chapel Hill] Newspaper, 1985 Oct. 23 (Box ACA-1)
    - Truck and Sign, Press Photo, 1985 Oct. 23 (Box ACA-1)
    - Price Begins Congress Campaign, Article, Chronicle, 1985 Oct. 24 (Box ACA-1)
    - Price Intends to Run a Positive..., Article, News of Orange Co., 1985 Oct. 23 (Box ACA-1)
    - Clifton Benson Endorses David Price, Article, News and Observer, 1985 Aug. 22 (Box ACA-1)
    - Price Off, Running..., Article, CH Newspaper, 1985 June 21 (Box ACA-1)
    - Politics: Analysis of 4th District Race (Box ACA-1)
    - Cobey, Bill, Quotes (Box ACA-1)
    - Politics
      - Ballot Security (Box ACA-1)
      - Democratic Party Direction, 2 folders (Box ACA-1)
    - Politics (Box ACA-2)
      - New Right (Box ACA-2)
      - Demo HQ, Republican Record (Box ACA-2)
      - Clean Campaign (Box ACA-2)
      - Gary Hart Material, 2 folders (Box ACA-2)
      - Ethics and Deavergate (Box ACA-2)
      - National Miscellaneous (Box ACA-2)
      - Populists (Box ACA-2)
      - Republican Propaganda (Box ACA-2)
      - Sanford/Broyhill (Box ACA-2)
    - Assorted Extra Clips (Box ACA-2)
    - Politics: PACs (Box ACA-2)
    - Politics: Stylistic Things (Box ACA-2)
    - Debate Prep (Box ACA-2)
    - Debates (Box ACA-2)
    - Debate Notes (Box ACA-2)
    - Other Articles / Cook and Southern Political Reports (Box ACA-2)
    - Farmers' Caravan (Box ACA-2)
    - Acid Rain, Textile Industry (Box ACA-2)
    - Nuke Dump Press #3 (Box ACA-2)
    - Saputo Letter and Answers, 2 folders (Box ACA-3)
    - National League of Savings (Box ACA-3)
    - Witness for Peace: Nicaragua (Box ACA-3)
    - Endorsement Names, Poll Watchers, Yard Sign, Lit. Drop Info, 2 folders (Box ACA-3)
    - Cobey
      - Franked Newsletters (Box ACA-3)
      - Direct Mail, 1986 May 12 (Box ACA-3)
      - Education (Box ACA-3)
      - Environment and Jordan Lake (Box ACA-3)
      - Far Right (Box ACA-3)
      - Coalition for Freedom, Taxpayers Educ. Foundation (Box ACA-3)
    - Wilma
      - [Woodard] - Publications, brochures, etc. (Box ACA-3)
      - Direct Mail (Box ACA-3)
      - Radio Ads (Box ACA-3)
    - Woody Webb: Radio Media Buy (Box ACA-3)
    - Kirsten [Nyrop] Radio Buy (Box ACA-3)
    - Woody TY Buy (Box ACA-3)
    - Wilma: TV Buy (Box ACA-3)
    - Cobey: TV Buy (Box ACA-3)
    - Cobey - Misc. (Box ACA-3)
    - Cobey: Office Info, Congress and Campaign (Box ACA-3)
    - Negative Cobey - collected pieces various (Box ACA-3)
    - Cobey News Releases (Box ACA-3)
    - Campaign Plans '86 (Box ACA-3)
    - Wilma
      - Run-off Issue (Box ACA-3)
      - 85 Session (Box ACA-4)
      - Computer Scam (Box ACA-4)
      - Press Releases (Box ACA-4)
    - Poll Notes (Box ACA-4)
    - Quotable Quotes - Cobey (Box ACA-4)
    - Cobey: Year of the Flag (Box ACA-4)
    - Woody: Direct Mail (Box ACA-4)
    - Statements: Woody Webb (Box ACA-4)
    - Kirsten Publication (Box ACA-4)
    - Woody Webb: Printed Matter (Box ACA-4)
    - Nyrop Packet (Box ACA-4)
    - Wilma
      - FEC [Federal Elections Commission] Report, 1986 Jan. 31, 2 folders (Box ACA-4)
      - Consumer Loan Issue (Box ACA-4)
      - Comparative Negligence (Box ACA-4)
      - Black Ad Sleaze (Box ACA-4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box ACA-4)
      - Announcement Speech (Box ACA-4)
    - Announcement Woody Webb (Box ACA-4)
    - Kirsten - Bio (Box ACA-4)
    - Kirsten Nyrop (Box ACA-4)
    - Woody FEC Report, 1986 Jan. 31 (Box ACA-4)
    - FEC Report - Britt, 1985 June 30 (Box ACA-4)
    - GOP: Press Releases (Box ACA-4)
    - International Trade (Box ACA-4)
    - Social Programs
      - Welfare (Box ACA-4)
      - Theory and Philosophy (Box ACA-4)
      - Social Security (Box ACA-4)
      - Blacks (Box ACA-4)
      - General Debate (Box ACA-4)
    - Social Problems
      - Homosexuals (Box ACA-4)
      - Handicapped (Box ACA-4)
      - Pornography (Box ACA-4)
      - Poverty-General (Box ACA-4)
    - Economy (Box ACA-5)
      - Monetary Policy, Banks (Box ACA-5)
      - Parental Leave Bill (Box ACA-5)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box ACA-5)
      - Rich v. Poor, Middle Class (Box ACA-5)
      - Savings and Loan Issues (Box ACA-5)
      - Small Business (Box ACA-5)
      - Economic Growth - South (Box ACA-5)
      - Taxation (Box ACA-5)
      - the South and N.C. (Box ACA-5)
      - Textiles (Box ACA-5)
      - Wealth Distribution (Box ACA-5)
    - Election Material (Box ACA-5)
    - NC Assoc. of Retired Federal Employees Mag. w/ Price answers (Box ACA-5)
    - N.C. Society for Autistic People (Box ACA-5)
    - Peace PAC Endorsement (Box ACA-5)
    - People for the American Way News Bulletin (Box ACA-5)
    - People for the American Way press conference on the Religious Right, 1986 Sept. 17 (Box ACA-5)
    - People for the American Way - Religious Intolerance (Box ACA-5)
    - Ministers' Forum, [1986] Oct. 14 (Box ACA-5)
    - Population Crisis Committee Voting Chart (Box ACA-5)
    - Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks Union endorsement (Box ACA-5)
    - [Miscellaneous] (Box ACA-5)
    - Senior citizens (Box ACA-5)
    - Sierra Club: Population and Growth info (Box ACA-5)
    - SANE National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy] Voting Record (Box ACA-5)
    - Price on the Issues (Box ACA-6)
    - Price: Newsletters (Box ACA-6)
    - Newsletter, Update Vol. 2, 1986 Apr. 15 (Box ACA-6)
    - Brochure, Strong Leadership For etc., 1986 Mar. 20 (Box ACA-6)
    - Newsletter, Price Update - Volunteer Push, 1986 Feb. 26 (Box ACA-6)
    - Price/Cobey, Mini Difference (Box ACA-6)
    - Price: Ad in Senior Citizens Voice (Box ACA-6)
    - State Employees Ad (Box ACA-6)
    - Franklin Times Ad (Box ACA-6)
    - NCAE - Printed Matter (Box ACA-6)
    - Southern International Perspectives (Box ACA-6)
    - Gary Hart - Issues Mailings (Box ACA-6)
    - Ed Jenkins (Box ACA-6)
    - Sen. Sam Nunn (Box ACA-6)
    - Cong. Rangel (Box ACA-6)
    - Charles Robb (Box ACA-6)
    - Jim Wright Background (Box ACA-6)
    - U.S. Chamber Letter (Box ACA-6)
    - Flyer, David Price: a Fresh Approach to Leadership, 1985 Summer (Box ACA-6)
    - Price Printed Matter (Box ACA-6)
    - Americans For Tax Reform - Pledge (Box ACA-6)
    - Price, PAC Booklet (Box ACA-6)
    - Newsletter, Update Vol. 3, 1986 July 10 (Box ACA-6)
    - Price: Brochures (Box ACA-6)
    - Print Ads (Box ACA-6)
    - Clippings (Box ACA-6)
    - Landmark Sleaze (Box ACA-7)
    - Southern Growth (Box ACA-7)
    - N.C. Senior Citizens Magazine, (Ad) (Box ACA-7)
    - Ruritan Club Ad, 1986 Sept. (Box ACA-7)
    - Govt. Employees Leaflet (Box ACA-7)
    - Canvass Piece, 1986 Sept. (Box ACA-7)
    - Carolina Country Magazine (Box ACA-7)
    - Ad Flack (Box ACA-7)
    - Ad Buys - WTVD letter (Box ACA-7)
    - N.C. Federal Retirees (Box ACA-7)
    - Durham Bulls Fund Raiser, 1986 May 29 (Box ACA-7)
    - Flyer, Progressives for Price, 1986 Apr. 30 (Box ACA-7)
    - Flyer, RWCA Post Card, 1986 Apr. 30 (Box ACA-7)
    - The Price Difference (Box ACA-7)
    - Price Difference Appendix: Originals (Box ACA-7)
    - Price: Literature (Box ACA-7)
    - Children's Service Newsletter w/ Price and Cobey answer (Box ACA-7)
    - Coalition for a Democratic Majority (Box ACA-7)
    - Handgun Control PAC (Box ACA-7)
    - LTV Corporation (members' handbook) (Box ACA-7)
    - NARAL info (Box ACA-7)
    - Letters to David (Box ACA-7)
    - House Votes (Box ACA-7)
    - Clippings, 2 folders (Box ACA-7)
    - Printed Materials (Box ACA-8)
    - Orange County - 86 Post Mortem (Box ACA-8)
    - Murray Fishel, Britt Report (Box ACA-8)
    - Budget (Box ACA-8)
    - Advisory Committee (Box ACA-8)
    - Steering Committee (Box ACA-8)
    - Endorsements and Campaigning (Box ACA-8)
    - Advertising Positive/Negative (Box ACA-8)
    - Cobey 1984 (Box ACA-8)
    - Cobey 1982 (Box ACA-8)
    - Issues-Comparison (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference - Nunn, 1986 Oct. 28 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Statement, Sen. Sasser Visit, Goodwin House, 1986 Oct. 27 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Statement, Sierra Club and Nuke Ad, Demo HQ, Raleigh, 1986 Oct. 24 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference, Illiteracy w/ Jim Cooper, Chapel Hill, 1986 Oct. 22 (Box ACA-8)
    - B'nai Brith Appearance (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Advisory, Nunn to Visit, 1986 Oct. 27 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference, Textiles w/ Ed Jenkins, Asheboro, 1986 Oct. 22 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference, Price Calls on Cobey to Remove Ad, Goodwin House, 1986, Oct. 21 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference, Cobey Sabotages Debate, Goodwin House, 1986 Oct. 20 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Release, FEC Report, 1986 Oct. 16 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference, Seniors for Price, K and W Cafeteria Raleigh, 1986 Oct. 15 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Release, Price to visit Franklin, 1986 Oct. 7 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference, Education, 1986 Oct. 7 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Release, Debates, 1986 Oct. 6 (Box ACA-8)
    - The Price Difference, Goodwin House, 1986 Oct. 2 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Advisory, Price to Visit Chatham Co., 1986 Oct. 1 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Statement, Governor Robb, Goodwin House, 1986 Sept. 27 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Statement, Asheboro High, 1986 Sept. 23 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Statement, Tax Reform - Cobey flip-flop, 1986 Sept. 22 (Box ACA-8)
    - Statement, Bruce Babbitt, YMCA, Raleigh, 1986 Sept. 19 (Box ACA-8)
    - Statement, Anti-Drug, South Africa, 1986 Sept. 15 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Release, Price responds to Cobey - tax increase, 1986 Sept. 11 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Statement, Fall kickoff, 1986 Sept. 8, 2 folders (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference, Congressman Wright, Morrisville, 1986 Sept. 6 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference, NCAE Endorsement, 1986 Sept. 5 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Release, Wright and kickoff (to Capitol press corps), 1986 Sept. 5 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press statement, Bradley Visits, 1986 Sept. 1 (Box ACA-8)
    - Media Advisory - Jim Wright's visit, 1986 Aug. 29 (Box ACA-8)
    - Media Advisory: Bradley to hold press conference, 1986 Aug. 29 (Box ACA-8)
    - Media Advisory: Fall Kickoff, 1986 Aug. 29 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Statement, Price on the Issues, 1986 Aug. 26 (Box ACA-8)
    - News Release, Price Questions Cobey Mailing at Taxpayers Expense, 1986 Aug. 15 (Box ACA-8)
    - Memo from Hobart to District Media, 1986 Aug. 15 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Release, Price Names Lawton as New Press Secretary, 1986 Aug. 13 (Box ACA-8)
    - Press Conference Statement, Tax Reform Petition, Demo HQ, 1986 Aug. 11 (Box ACA-8)